ROBERT MISCHIE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Bristol United Kingdom

PHONE

07456232657

EMAIL

mischie_robert@yahoo.com

LINKS

Personal Website

<u>Github</u>

LinkedIn

SKILLS

SCSS

Python

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Materialize CSS

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

jQuery

React

LANGUAGES

German

• • • 0 0

English

• • • •

Romanian

• • • •

PROFILE

My name is Robert Mischie, I am 19 years old and I am a Computer Science student at UWE Bristol. I am a passionate web developer that is proefficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and has been programming for 3 years and web developing for 1 year.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Fullstack Web Developer, Programming Shortcuts

Bristol, United Kingdom

Jan 2021 — Present

Building QR code E-commerce Menus for local businesses where the clients can order and the manager can view everything in a Dashboard.

Frontend Web Developer, ziOXII's Studio

Drobeta Turnu Severin, Romania

Jul 2020 — Aug 2020

Built landing pages for the local businesses with HTML,CSS,JavaScript and Materialize CSS framework by looking at Adobe XD files and recreating the design.

EDUCATION

High School diploma, Gheorghe Titeica National College

Drobeta-Turnu Severin

2016 — 2020

Graduated in the Computer Science field

BSc Computer Science, University of the West of England, Bristol

Bristol

2020 - 2023

Currently enrolled as a freshman in Computer Science

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hackaton

Drobeta-Turnu Severin

Won 1st place on a local hackaton by building an app that retrieves data from football matches in real time using an API.

C# Regional Olympiad

Drobeta-Turnu Severin

Honourable mention

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Available on my website www.robertmischie.com